<?xml version='1.0' ?>
<Members>
    <Member>
        <Sno>1</Sno>
        <Name><![CDATA[Adhalrao Patil,  Shri Shivaji]]></Name>
        <memberId><![CDATA[4143]]></memberId>
        <Constituencies><![CDATA[Shirur (Maharashtra)]]></Constituencies>
        <Party><![CDATA[Shiv Sena]]></Party>
        <FatherName><![CDATA[Shri  Dattatray Kondaji Adhalrao Patil]]></FatherName>
        <MotherName><![CDATA[Smt. Chandrabhaga Dattatray Adhalrao]]></MotherName>
        <DateOfBirth><![CDATA[08/05/1956]]></DateOfBirth>
        <PlaceOfBirth><![CDATA[Landewadi, Taluka Ambegaon,  Pune (Maharashtra)]]></PlaceOfBirth>
        <MaritalStatus><![CDATA[Married]]></MaritalStatus>
        <DateOfMarriage><![CDATA[02-04-1980 00:00:00]]></DateOfMarriage>
        <SpouseName><![CDATA[Smt. Kalpana Adhalrao Patil]]></SpouseName>
        <NoOfSon><![CDATA[2]]></NoOfSon>
        <NoOfDaughter><![CDATA[0]]></NoOfDaughter>
        <EducatQualification><![CDATA[Intermediate (Arts)  Educated at Shivaji University, Kolhapur, Maharashtra]]></EducatQualification>
        <Profession><![CDATA[Industrialist]]></Profession>
        <Paddress><![CDATA[At &amp; P.O. Landewadi, Tal. Ambegaon,  Distt. Pune-410503, Maharashtra]]></Paddress>
        <Localaddress><![CDATA[59, Lodhi Estate,  New Delhi - 110 003]]></Localaddress>
        <SocialActivity><![CDATA[Organised a two days workshop on `Entrepreneurship Development` at Landewadi, District Pune, Maharashtra in 1996 for the career guidance and encouragement of entrepreneurs from rural part of Pune ; organised a workshop of NRI and Industrialists of Maharashtra on behalf of JMCCI held in 1995 which was attended by more than three hundred NRIs from U.S.A and U.K.; organised `Industrious Maharashtra Exhibition` in 1994 held in Vigyan Bhavan, New Delhi; successfully led the delegation of 92 Industrialists from Maharashtra to U.S.A. in 1995 on behalf of Jagatik Marathi Chamber of Commerce &amp; Industries]]></SocialActivity>
        <SpecialInterests><![CDATA[Promotion of entrepreneurship in rural areas; upliftment of tribal and poorer sections; promotion of  agricultural development and productivity; literature reading; cricket; travelling; promoting education in rural areas]]></SpecialInterests>
        <FavouritePasstime><![CDATA[Reading, Travelling, Listening to Classical Music, Folk Dances]]></FavouritePasstime>
        <SportsAndClubs><![CDATA[Cricket, Football and Golf]]></SportsAndClubs>
        <CountryVisite><![CDATA[Widely Travelled]]></CountryVisite>
        <EmailID><![CDATA[shivajirao@sansad.nic.in ; 
 shivajirao@vsnl.com; ]]></EmailID>
        <State><![CDATA[Maharashtra]]></State>
        <Freedom><![CDATA[NO]]></Freedom>
        <OtherInfo><![CDATA[Received `Dahanukar Entrepreneur Award`- in 1989 from Maharashtra Chamber of Commerce and Industry, Mumbai; `Best Industrialist Award from Small Scale Sector` - in 1991 from National Federation of Indian Engineers, Delhi. ; `Most Successful SSI Unit of 1993 Award` - from Bombay Industries Association, Mumbai; `Successful Small Scale Company for the Year Award` - in 1993 from Institute of Marketing Management (IMM), Delhi.; `Outstanding Leadership &amp; Devoted Service to Instrument Industry` - in 1994 from IDEMI, Mumbai; `Samaj Bhushan` Award - from Khilari Pratishtan in 1997; First Generation Entrepreneur - award by Entrepreneur`s International; Yashodeep Puraskar of Late Sau Shevantabai Shirode Smruti, awarded by the Institution of Engineers (India) on Engineer`s Day on 18<sup>th</sup> September 1999;  Founder Chairman  Shree Bhairavnath Shikshan Prasarak Mandal, , Shivaji D. Adhalrao Patil Vidyalaya (Marathi medium), , Bhairavnath Nagari Sahkari Patsanstha Maryadit, Landewadi, District Pune; (iv) M/s. Dynalog (India) Ltd., Mumbai;  Chairman,  Adhalrao Patil Management and Research Institute; , Deccan Maratha College of Science; , Bhimashankar B.Ed. College; (iv) Shivaji Adhalrao D.Ed. College; (v) Blue Bell Prep School, Landewadi; (vi) Shivaji Adhalrao Patil Vidyalaya; and (vii) New English School;  Ex-Chairman,  Bhimashankar Sahakari Sakhar Karkhana, Ambegaon, District Pune; Executive President , Jagatik Marathi Chamber of Commerce &amp; Industries (JMCCI); President, Marleshwar Rural and Education Centres Dryaneshwar Vidya Mandir, Lanja, Ratnagiri; <i>Vice-President,</i> National Centre for Rural Development (NCRD), Pune, 1992-2003]]></OtherInfo>
    </Member>
</Members>